{
    "subject": "resource/Signs_(band)",
    "predicate": "property/yearsActive",
    "object": "1999",
    "human_readable": "Signs (band) was active from 1999.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6775805354118347,
            "question": "What year did Signs (band) begin their activity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.660934329032898,
            "question": "Is Signs (band) still active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6007412672042847,
            "question": "Where is Signs (band) from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44841715693473816,
            "question": "Who are the members of Signs (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42530009150505066,
            "question": "During which decade was Signs (band) most popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3990722894668579,
            "question": "What were some of the major events happening in the world when Signs (band) began their activity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3840538263320923,
            "question": "What genre of music is Signs (band) known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24003541469573975,
            "question": "Has Signs (band) released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22307640314102173,
            "question": "Have Signs (band) won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1889204978942871,
            "question": "What are some of Signs (band)'s most popular songs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Signs (band) was active from 1999.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2167_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Have Signs (band) won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2167_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Signs (band) released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2167_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Signs (band) known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2167_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2167_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Signs (band) was active from 1999\" in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about the Tedeschi Trucks Band, which has a studio album called \"Signs\". The documents mention that the band formed in 2010 and that \"Signs\" is their fourth studio release. There is no mention of the band being active from 1999."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information suggesting that the band \"Signs\" was active from 1999. In fact, the documents mention that \"Signs\" is the fourth studio album by Tedeschi Trucks Band and was released in February 2019, which contradicts the query stating it was active from 1999."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context provided does not mention any information about the formation year of Tedeschi Trucks Band, so we cannot determine if they were active from 1999 or not.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that the album \"Signs\" is their fourth studio record since forming in 2010.  This directly contradicts the claim of being active from 1999.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Tedeschi Trucks Band was formed in 2010, not 1999.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the Tedeschi Trucks Band formed in 2010, not 1999.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}